【家長提示】本片的評級為 TV-14-DLSV，
可能包含暗示性對話、粗俗語言、性相關情境和暴力等內容，
因而不建議 14 歲以下兒童獨自觀賞。
這樣的結局對我們很不利  蓋瑞
The outcome was never in our favor, Gary.
你就直說了吧  HUE
Cut it to me straight, HUE.
我還有辦法脫離這個混亂的局面嗎？
What are my chances of getting out of this mess?
根據你當前的狀態
In your current state,
你將在10分鐘後經過復原點
you will pass the point of recovery in 10 minutes.
你的氧氣也發生了洩漏  蓋瑞
You are also leaking O2, Gary.
氧氣
啊  你瞧瞧
Huh, look at that.
氧氣
明明是紅色警報  用的卻是綠色
They went with green for a red alert.
要是換做我的話就會用紅色了
I mean, I would have went with red,
或者長青花色
a periwinkle.
就算是蛋奶酒色也好啊
Heck, I mean, even egg nog.
有沒有這種顏色我不知道
I don't even know if that's a color,
但是  蒼天啊  真想來杯蛋奶酒
but, oh, good Lord, now I just want egg nog.
以當前的洩漏速度  你將會在9分鐘後失去生命徵象
The rate of the leak will render you lifeless in nine minutes.
你還真是「好消息」不斷啊
You are really buttering me up with fantastic news.
蓋瑞  在可預見的範圍內
I'm afraid, Gary,
你恐怕已經沒有生還的機會了
there is no foreseeable outcome where you survive.
真是買錯門票了  偏偏買到了這麼遠的地方
These tickets suck -- right in the nosebleeds.
※在美國和加拿大英語中，「nosebleed section」或「nosebleed seats」常用來代指距離活動區域最遠的座位。此用法源於高海拔地區因低氣壓造成的鼻出血症狀。
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
托德星雲     463G區
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
翻譯版本
v1.0.1-CHT
翻譯
SerCom_KC
蓋瑞船長
校對
旗木佐罗
Aah!
早上好  蓋瑞
Good morning, Gary.
今天是第1818日
Day 1,818.
校對
落单的Finn
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1817日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
第1818日
太空溫度：-273.15℃
飛船溫度：20℃（標況）
我他媽拒絕
How about freakin' no?
你這次不是一般的狠啊  HUE
That was a bit harder than normal, HUE!
校對
万俟猫
時間軸
SerCom_KC
特效
蓋瑞到此一遊
修訂
玻璃心沙包
你好  親愛的朋友
Hello, dear friend.
好久不見
It's been a while.
漢克！太好了
Hank! Yes!
最近怎樣啊  漢克？
What's up, Hank?
嗯  是啊
Hmm, yeah.
貝絲今天確實很美
Beth is looking good today.
貝絲
你看啊  那雙熱辣的眼睛直勾勾地盯著我看
Look at that. Staring at me with those hot eyes.
你  我  等會見
You, me... later.
打牌嗎  漢克？來玩牌嗎？
Cards, Hank? You want to play?
翻譯項目位址
translatedby.sercomkc.org/finalspace
我要找個人陪我打牌  所以就決定是你了
I need somebody to play with. So it's gonna be you.
Aah!
本翻譯作品按照CC BY-NC-SA 4.0授權條款向公眾授權
未經授權禁止用於任何商業用途
我的手牌都快沒了  漢克
I'm starting to run out of decks, Hank.
嘿  蓋瑞  你好呀
Hey, Gary! Hello!
哦  餅乾  好吃的餅乾
Ooh, cookie, yummy!
Ha!
HUE？
HUE?
什麼事  蓋瑞？
Yes, Gary?
我能要一片餅乾嗎？
Can I have a cookie?
嗯  不行  蓋瑞
Mm, no, Gary.
為什麼不行？
Why not?
你都給KVN吃了
You opened it for KVN.
那個死糞球根本就吃不了餅乾
That sack of wet turds can't even eat cookies!
就只會把餅乾往他處理器插槽上撞
He just smashes it into his processor slot.
我討厭KVN  真心討厭
I hate KVN... so painfully.
遇上他真是我人生的不幸
He's the blight of my life.
如果你要拿餅乾
If you take a cookie,
按照規定  我要將你的刑期再延長一天
I will be forced to add one full day to your sentence.
你覺得區區一天的時間能嚇到一個船長嗎？
You think a full day scares the captain?
蓋瑞  過去五年來的每一天
Gary, I've explained this to you every day
我一直都在跟你解釋這個問題
for the past five years.
你並不是船長
You are not the captain.
你只是這艘船上的一名囚犯
You are a prisoner aboard this ship.
好像是有這麼一回事
Sounds vaguely familiar.
快點  打開櫃子
Now, open this cabinet.
哦  真的是好好吃
Oh, they're just so-o-o-o good!
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
Aaaah!
你的刑期再延長一天
One day has been added to your sentence.
噢！我碰到了！
Oh! I touched one!
船長碰到餅乾了！
The captain's touched one!
船長日誌80085
Captain's log 80085.
嘿  奎恩  瞧瞧我是誰
Hey, Quinn! Guess who!
是我  蓋瑞  我又來了
It's me, Gary, again.
奎恩  我好好想了一下
Quinn, I've thought on it,
今天是一個重要的日子
and I've decided that since this is a big day,
是我們的紀念日  所以我決定
the day of our anniversary, as you know,
是時候展現我的真心了
it's time to get real.
奎恩  這…這就是真正的  毫無修飾的蓋瑞
Quinn, this -- this is the real raw Gary.
為了把我真實的一面藏起來  不讓你看見
It's been eating me up inside
我真的費了很大的力氣
keeping the real raw Gary from you.
整整五年來
For five years,
你一直都縈繞在真正蓋瑞的精神堡壘裡  揮之不去
real raw Gary hasn't been able to get you out of his mind fortress.
第一次見到你的那天
When I met you that day,
我就知道你是我命中註定的那個人
I knew you were it.
把我們的東西還回來  蓋瑞！
Give us what's ours, Gary!
講道理  布魯斯汀博士  還有德里克
Technically, it's mine!
這東西明明是我的
Dr. Bluesteen and Derek!
地球     五年前
你該減減肥了！
Lose some weight!
德里克  快點  跟緊了
Come on, Derek, keep up!
居然給我一瓶蘇打水？
They gave me a seltzer?
為什麼他們要給我一瓶蘇打水？
Why would they give me a seltzer?
一定是我訂了一瓶  我訂了嗎？
... unless I ordered it -- Did I order it?
沒錯  訂了
Yes, I did!
我一定要敲爛你的膝蓋  蓋瑞
I'm gonna break your knees, Gary!
甜天火
Sweet heavenly fire.
那邊那位頂靚又火辣的女生是誰啊？
Who is the muy bueno super spicy lady?
那是奎恩·艾岡隊長  不過你就別去自討苦吃了
Captain Quinn Airgone. But don't bother.
既然你不是無疆守護的成員  那你肯定跟她無緣的
If you're not Infinity Guard, she's not interested.
說句大實話  我在上邊的官職還真他媽不小哦
Actually, I'm pretty freaking high up in the command chain.
真的？
Really?
對啊  真的
Yeah, really.
講真的？
Seriously?
講真的  你臉靠太近了  老兄
Seriously, I can't get any closer to your face, dude.
那你的制服到哪裡去了  夥計？
Then where's your uniform, bud?
我有制服  小子
I have one, guy.
你根本就沒有吧  朋友
No, you don't, pal.
我就是有  死黨
Yes, I do, chum!
就在…洗手間裡  媽的
It's... in the bathroom. Crap!
Shwa!
看起來不錯喔  蓋瑞
Looking good, Gary!
把他丟在這裡不管就好啦
You're just gonna leave him in there,
你這丟…你這丟人的傢伙！
you chuck -- you chuck-face!
哎呀  有阿斯匹靈喔
Oh, sweet aspirin.
三個德拉特諾  零錢剛剛好
Three dratnoids, exact change!
爽
Tight!
吞下去
Swallow!
你是個大好人喔  蓋瑞
You're a good guy, Gary.
現在穩如…
Now to be smooth as --
Uh! Uh!
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
招呼都沒打就拿到女生的電話
First time I got a girl's number
這還真是頭一遭呢
before I even said "Hey."
我說  我就喜歡你這樣的
You see, I like that.
電話號碼超多的女生
I like a girl with a lot of phones.
我這裡寫的是普朗克常數中一個矛盾的解
Actually, this is the solution to an internal inconsistency
這個問題一直都沒人處理
in Planck's constant that's never been solved
因為就算是到了今天  都沒有人覺得這是個大麻煩
because until now, no one realized it was a problem.
還有  說到大麻煩
And speaking of problems,
如果你不想變成一個大麻煩的話  就請你離開
maybe you should leave before you become one --
立刻馬上
as in now.
或者我可以請你一杯
Or I could buy you a drink.
真的？
Really?
不如我們瘋狂一點
Let's get wild.
你請我一杯怎麼樣？
How about you buy me a drink?
天哪
Wow.
我的意思是不行  但你這話…天哪
I mean, no. But wow.
全體無疆守護人員
All Infinity Guards,
立即返回基地報告
report back to base immediately.
走了！
Let's go!
回你那裡？
Back to your place?
你移動的速度就像獵豹一樣快
You're moving at cheetah speeds.
我喜歡
I like it.
趕緊去開你的F71飛鷹  飛行員同志
You have an F71 Hawk to fly, pilot.
完了  炸了
Oh, my crap.
飛行員  立即啟動飛鷹
Move this Hawk, pilot.
你能做到的  蓋瑞
You can do this, Gary.
讓智商飛躍吧
Become a much smarter person now.
完了  徹底炸了！
Oh, my double crap!
你根本就不是飛行員吧
You're not a pilot, are you?
我是…啊
Yes, I am.
吃我一拳！
Punch!
得到教訓了
Lesson learned.
如果你想在政府面前搞事的話
If you ever want to piss off a whole government,
只需要轟掉92艘星際巡洋艦
just take out 92 star cruisers
和一家墨西哥家族餐館就夠了
and a small family-owned Mexican restaurant.
對不住了  瓜達盧普
Sorry, Guadalupe.
Hyuh!
Wah!
嘿  蓋瑞  我叫KVN
Hey, Gary. My name is KVN.
我是你的深太空防精神錯亂伴侶
I'm your deep space insanity avoidance companion.
很高興見到你
Nice to meet you.
我已經開始討厭你了
I already hate you.
好消息是  我在這個可悲的修羅場裡的刑期
The good news is that I only have a week left to my sentence
只剩下一個星期了
aboard this pathetic rat's nest.
發送！
And send!
HUE  她這次肯定會回覆的
She's gonna respond this time, HUE.
有很大的概率她不會回覆
There is a high probability she will not.
但也有很小的概率她會回覆
But there's still a low probability she will.
肯定是
I'll take it!
Ha ha ha ha!
搞定！
Nailed it!
還有四個陣列需要維修
There are still four arrays that need to be repaired.
別纏著我了  HUE
Get off my cheeks, HUE.
別纏著我了  蓋瑞
Get off my cheeks, Gary.
1891-C恢復連線
1891-C is back online.
HUE  那個  今天還是星期四吧
HUE, by any chance, is it still Thursday?
星期四已經持續了72小時
It's been Thursday for the last 72 hours.
太好了  看來還在播
Sweet. Then it's still on.
我是愛德華多·蒙托亞·塔拉金多·塔·拉卡拉·伯利亞
My name is Eduardo Montoya Talakinto Ta Lacara Poligia.
你殺了我的父親  準備受死吧
You killed my father. Prepare to die.
蓋瑞  休息時間到
Gary, your break is over.
但是那個殺死愛德華多·塔拉金多·塔拉·帕西亞父親的小子
But the guy who killed Eduardo Talakinto Tala Pacia's father
還沒準備受死呢
hasn't prepared to die yet!
天啊  有個…有個像素點跳來跳去的
Dang, there's a -- there's a pixel on the loose.
Whoo!
Oh!
外星人撞我臉上了啦
It's an alien on my face!
外星人撞我…外星臉啦
It's an alien on my -- it's a face alien!
Aaaahh!
哦  你沒吃我的臉  你是在抱我的臉啊
Oh. You're not a face-eater, you're a face-hugger.
Chookity.
我正缺一個抱臉的人呢
I need a face-hugger in my life.
Whoa!
你讓我想起了很久以前  我曾經的一個朋友
You remind me of a friend I used to have a long time ago.
月餅
「月餅」這個名字  你覺得怎麼樣？
How do you like the name Mooncake?
Whoa!
那我就叫你「月餅」了
Mooncake it is.
我好興奮  超興奮的
I'm pumped -- super-excited.
你應該不會突然說人話吧
You don't by chance speak real words, do you?
Chookity pok.
哈！那也行
Ha! Works for me.
兆壓     18650區
歡迎
Welcome.
天啊  你居然這麼小  我的媽
You're so tiny, man! What -- oh!
等會趕緊告訴別人去
Wait until the guys hear about this.
請坐
Sit.
到底在哪裡？
Where is it?!
什麼？
What?!
E-351
E-351.
我…我不知道
I -- I don't know.
我絕不會對您撒謊  總司令
I would never lie to you, Lord Commander.
真的  真的是…
You know, it's just --
對不起  但你實在是太矮了
I'm sorry, you're just so small!
真的  真的…
It's -- it's...
Wah!
在哪裡發現的？
Where did you find it?
我沒去找
I didn't.
是它找到的我
It found me.
那個HUE
The less HUE --
別告訴別人  那傢伙其實有點神經質
who, between us, is a bit of a dickly-wont --
最好不能被那傢伙知道你的存在
knows about you, the better.
好了  你就呆在這裡吧
Okay, let's get you in here.
好了嗎？
You ready?
Chookity!
Chookity, chookity!
給我關上啊
Please close.
好吧  關不上  這招沒用
Okay, it's not fitting. It's not working.
我有時候就藏在這裡  就像一個床墊幽靈一樣
I hide there sometimes. I'm like a mattress ghost.
千萬別告訴別人
Don't tell anyone.
Ooh.
哦  完美！完…
Oh, perfect! Per--
不  一點都不完美
No, it's not perfect.
太爛了  為什麼就這麼爛
Just... that sucks. Why does that suck so hard?!
好吧  要不然這樣
Okay, how about this?
有時候我想逃…我想逃避自己的時候
Sometimes I'd hide -- I'd like to hide from myself
隱  藏
就會把內褲像這樣在自己頭上套一圈
by putting underwear on the circumference of my head.
怎麼樣？合適嗎？
How about that? How's it fit?
Chookity.
完美
Perfect.
就…直接…殺了…我吧！
Please... just... kill... me!
我不會這麼做的  那樣就太粗魯了
Wouldn't think of it. That would be rude.
吃掉
Eat.
HUE  到底什麼情況？
HUE, what is going on?
為什麼整個飛船在開一場無聲的狂歡舞會？
Why has the ship turned into a silent dance rave?
四架無法識別的飛行器
Four unknown vessels
正在朝我們所在的位置降落
are descending upon our location.
根據飛船上的標記  我推斷
The markings lead me to believe
他們是來自凡特克西的賞金獵人
they are Ventrexian bounty hunters.
好雞凍啊  來了幾個複雜生命體
Twist my nipples rough, we're talking complex life-forms.
好  HUE  你一定要問問他們打不打牌
Yes! HUE, you must find out if they play cards.
這個問題很重要  很重要啊  HUE
I need this! I need this, HUE!
我…我真的想找個人陪我打
I -- I really need somebody to play with.
啟動安全協定
Activating security protocol.
HUE  你他媽在做什麼？
HUE, what the crap?!
為了你的安全考慮
For your own safety,
你必須留在飲食區
you must remain in the commissary.
為了我的安全考慮？
For my own safety?
五年來第一次有人來找我們
We get our first visitors in five years,
而我卻不能跟他們搭話？
and I can't mingle with them?
HUE  馬上開門  我需要交流
HUE, open this door right now! I need to mingle!
抱歉  我不能開門
I'm afraid I cannot.
你最好抱歉地給我開門
You better afraid me up an open door!
喔  讓KVN來幫你吧
Ooh, let KVN help!
媽媽咪啊  KVN
God almighty, KVN!
能不能不要這麼神出鬼沒的啊
You can't just phantom up on me like that!
不要慌  我是來幫你的
Don't worry about me, I am helping.
噢噢  KVN  你總算做了件好事
Oh, oh. KVN, you did something right!
Ohh!
KVN  你這個嘰嘰喳喳的可怕電腦！
KVN, you processed horrendous nest of tweets!
我們需要在你的飛行器上搜尋樣本E-351
Your vessel has been subjected to a search for specimen E-351.
馬上出來  否則死路一條
Come forward... or die.
噢  糟了
Oh, crap.
我的手臂啊
My arm, man!
Aaahh!
愚蠢的東西
You fool!
這個傢伙又是什麼鬼？
Who the freak is this guy?
我認為他們想要被你藏在
I believe they want the alien
背包裡的那個外星人
you're hiding in your backpack.
什麼？我不知道你在說什麼
What? I don't know what you're referring to.
這正是我生命的意義
This is what I was meant to do!
我從來都沒有如此真切地感受到自己的存在
I have never felt so alive!
你是說我的內褲小夥伴啊
Oh! You mean my underpants caddy.
是的  我們應當滿足他們的要求  蓋瑞
Yes. We should comply with their wishes, Gary.
我不太確定  我有點開始喜歡這個小傢伙了
I don't know. I kind of was starting to like this little guy.
他的抱抱好舒服
He gives great hugs.
蓋瑞  我們的裝備不足以應對這樣的威脅
Gary, we are not equipped to face this threat.
做得好  阿瓦卡多
Good job, Avocato.
這場鬥爭跟我們無關
This is not our fight.
HUE  它就是跟我們有關
HUE, we make it our fight.
你是無疆守護的一員  保護生命可是你的座右銘啊
You're Infinity Guard. Your whole motto is to protect life.
那能算作生命嗎  蓋瑞？
Is that life, Gary?
如果它都不算的話  那我不就是個只會咆哮的瘋子了
Well, if it isn't, then I'm a raging sack of walnuts!
HUE  立即開始光折
HUE, lightfold the ship!
這樣做的話  你的刑期將會被延長
This will lengthen your sentence.
我知道  立即開始光折  HUE
I get it. Lightfold the ship, HUE!
蓋瑞
Gary.
快點
Do it!
他們要開始光折了
They're lightfolding!
防護盾已開啟
即將開始光折
迫近警告  迫近警告
Proximity alert. Proximity alert.
那個真的是那個嗎？
Is that what I think it is?
HUE  這可不妙  趕緊離開這裡
HUE, that's no good. Get us out of here.
再光折一次  光折  光折！
Lightfold again, lightfold, lightfold!
在光折引擎冷卻完畢之前  我們無法移動
We are immobilized until the lightfold engines cool.
引
擎
碰
撞
迫
近
警
告
飛船將於29秒後遭遇小行星帶
The asteroids will reach the ship in 29 seconds.
立即戴好頭盔
Secure your helmet immediately.
我的頭盔還在氣閘那裡
My helmet's in the airlock.
快跑  距離遭遇還有15秒
Run. 15 seconds until impact.
以你目前的速度  你將無法趕上
At your current pace, you will not make it.
噢  蓋瑞就是趕得上
Oh, Gary will make it.
嘿  蓋瑞  抱歉  現在有空嗎
Hey, Gary, sorry, got a minute?
那個  我一直在想…
Yeah, I've been thinking about...
Hyah!
蓋瑞  2秒
Gary, two seconds.
一定要活下來  一定要活下來
You're gonna live! You're gonna live!
餓地神啊  這次絕對死定了
Sweet Grandor's glove! Definitely gonna die this time!
蓋瑞  你可能有麻煩
Gary, you may have a problem.
你這個「可能有」的用詞很有問題欸
I seriously question your usage of "may have."
我看我們「已經有」麻煩了
I think we have reached have.
而且還是「相當有」麻煩啊
I am very deep in have!
受行星的引力影響
Due to the moon's gravity,
銀河一號將於大約39秒後再次遭遇小行星帶
the asteroid field will swing back to the Galaxy One
之後便會輪到你
and then at you in approximately 39 seconds.
這可麻煩了  HUE
That's no good, HUE.
幫我規劃一下解決方案
Formulate me up some solutions.
計算中
Calculating.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Ahh.
蓋瑞  我有一個方案
Gary, I do have a solution
但只有33%的成功率
with a 33% chance of success.
好吧  具體內容是？
Okay, and that would be?
讓你的氧氣倉進行一次緊急噴氣
Perform an emergency air blow-out of your O2 tanks.
如果你能進入行星軌道
If you can enter the moon's orbit,
你就有可能繞其旋轉  返回銀河一號
you might be able to sling-hook around it back to the Galaxy One.
好吧  好吧  就這麼辦
All right. All right, let's do this.
蓋瑞  你應該清楚
Gary, you should know,
這個計算結果只適用於你一個人
this calculation will only work with you.
你必須拋棄那個生命體
You will have to leave the life-form behind.
月餅？
Mooncake?
否則  你能活著返回銀河一號的可能性為零
Or there is zero probability you will make it back to the Galaxy One alive.
我知道了  管他那麼多
I get it. I'll screw them at you.
我就是要帶著月餅走
Mooncake is coming with.
你絕對無法成功  蓋瑞
You will never make it, Gary.
獨自一人完成這次移動是你唯一的選擇
Your only chance is to perform this maneuver alone.
HUE  你這種缺乏自信的做法非常讓人不爽
HUE, your lack of confidence is positively depressing!
氣倉噴氣倒計時  三
Blowing the air tank in three...
關閉保險
緊急噴氣
蓋瑞  拜託了
Gary, please.
緊急噴氣
二
Two...
你會失敗的
You will fail.
你說的沒錯
You're right.
我會失敗…
I will fail...
敗出精彩
upwards.
正在進入行星軌道
Entering into moon's orbit.
不好  撐不住了
Oh, no! It's not working.
以你當前的速率
At your current rate of velocity,
你將無法返回銀河一號
you will not make it back to the Galaxy One.
銀河一號
速度不足
你失敗了  蓋瑞
You have failed, Gary.
距離小行星帶遭遇時間還有5秒
The asteroids will make impact in five seconds.
四
Four...
月餅
三
Three...
月餅
氧氣
二
Two...
氧氣
一
One.
成功了
It worked!
HUE  是你說的我會死
HUE! And you said I could die!
Ha!
你確實死了  五分鐘
You were dead -- for five minutes.
開什麼玩笑
Are you for serious?
我認為是那個生命體救了你一命
I believe the life-form saved your life.
月餅？
Mooncake?
Chookity, chookity.
謝謝你救了我一命
Thank you for saving my life.
Wow.
檢測到飛船上仍有一個無法識別的生命體
I am detecting one unknown life-form still aboard.
他有武裝
He is armed.
哪個船艙？
What deck?
4A  機器人正在前往那裡
4A. Sames are already on route.
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
今天是
星期一
我討厭KVN
蓋瑞船長
把E-351交出來
Hand over E-351.
聽著  兄弟  我只問一句話
Listen, buddy, I only have one thing to say to you.
你會打牌嗎？
Do you play cards?
就當你會了
I'm gonna take that as a yes!
不許動
Freeze!
啊  老天爺
Oh, good Lord!
我的媽呀
Oh, my gosh.
能不能不要像那樣突然靠近一個人啊  漢克
Just don't walk up on somebody like that, Hank!
我差點就尿出來了
I'm gonna crap my pants.
我還以為你是嬰鬼還是鬼嬰
I thought you were a baby ghost or a ghost baby
還是某種鬼嬰的幻象
or something in between the ghost baby spectrum.
不准動
Freeze!
Aagh!
媽的  漢克
Freakin' crap, Hank!
這不挺好的嗎？
Isn't this great?
就我們兩個大男人坐在這裡  悠哉悠哉打牌
I mean, just us guys sitting here, chillin', playin' cards.
你是不是欠揍啊  白癡
[You really want to fight, idiot?!]
你倒還真是話多啊  喵星人
You really know how to sling the zingers, cat guy.
我叫阿瓦卡多
The name's Avocato.
不  你就叫人生輸家
No. The name is loser!
吃我四條
Eat it! Four of a kind!
你總不會沒注意到吧
You're oblivious to this thing, aren't you?
什麼？
What?
那個
That.
這個？
This?
對  就那個
Yes! That.
月餅？
Mooncake?
月餅是指什麼？
What's a Mooncake?
這個啊
This!
那個？
That?
沒錯  就那個
Yes, that.
別告訴我你還給E-351取了名字
Please tell me you didn't name E-351.
E-3559是什麼東西？
What's an E-3559?
那個
That.
這個？
This?
對  他媽的就是那個
Yes, freakin' that!
我當然注意到了
I suppose I did.
你根本就不知道那是什麼東西吧
You don't know what that is, do you?
那可是行星殺手
That is a planet-killer.
你聽到了嗎？
Are you hearing this?
這個奇葩居然認為月餅是行星殺手
Freakin' guy thinks Mooncake is a planet-killer!
真是天大…我的媽呀
What a freakin' -- oh, man!
把你的插槽閉上  KVN  媽的
Shut your face hole, KVN! Crap.
你覺得我是說著玩？我可是認真的
So you think this is funny? I'm serious.
有嗎？
Are you?
當然  「總司令」為了它搜遍了整個星系
Yes. The Lord Commander is searching the galaxy for it.
你藏不住的  無論你逃到哪裡  他都能夠找到你
You can't hide. Wherever you go, he'll find you.
憑什麼我要相信你說的話  鬍鬚仔
Why should I believe you, Mr. Whiskers?
再敢這麼叫我  我就殺了你
Call me that again, and I'll kill you.
嗯哼  我侮辱了你
Mm-hmm. I've insulted you.
你看  事情是這樣
You see, the truth is,
我從來沒跟貓人打過交道
I've never socialized with a cat man before.
我的鄰居養過一隻貓  它天天都會舔自己
My neighbor had a cat. Loved to lick himself.
你該不會也有這個習慣吧
You're not gonna do that, right?
有的話  可就是個大問題了  朋友
Otherwise, we're gonna have problems, friend.
我不是貓  我是一個凡特克西人
I'm not a cat, I'm a Ventrexian.
這樣啊  那我還是長老教人呢
Got it. See, I'm a Presbyterian myself.
但我普愛眾生
But I love all people.
我就是這麼長大的
Just how I was raised.
我們都有危險
We're in danger.
聽好  我們所有人都有危險
Listen, all of us are in danger!
月餅  看著蓋瑞閃閃發光的大眼睛
Mooncake, look into Gary's gelatinous marbles.
只要我還有一口氣
As long as I draw breath
如果你能夠帶給我無窮無盡的冒險旅程
and you provide me with copious amounts of adventure,
我就一定陪著你到最後
I will be there for you.
現在我們是一個團隊
We're a team now.
你就來做我的跟班
And I'll let you be my sidekick and such
再讓那個誰當你的超級手下
with a super side order of what-not.
說得太好了
Well said.
享用餅乾吧
餅乾…給我的嗎？
A cookie -- for me?!
享用餅乾吧
沒錯  蓋瑞  拿一片吧
Yes, Gary. Take one.
享用餅乾吧
你展示了此前我從未看到過的一面  勇氣
You displayed a quality I hadn't seen in you previously -- courage.
你是個很好的榜樣  這是你贏得的
Exemplary. You earned it.
而且因為我就是船長
And because I am the captain.
餅乾收回
Cookie withdrawn.
Aah!
悔悟之人必能成
The penitent man shall pass.
Ohh!
我拿到了！
I got one!
餓地神啊
Sweet Grandor's glove,
拿到我它娘的餅乾啦
I got a mother-loving cookie!
這是一片餅乾  奎恩
This is a cookie, Quinn.
HUE說這是我贏得的  因為我成了事  奎恩
HUE said I earned it because I did things, Quinn.
危險的事情  能贏餅乾的事情
Dangerous things. Cookie-earning things.
現在  是時候享用我的榮耀果實了
Now to eat the fruits of my greatness.
我的了
Mine!
什麼？不
What? No!
KVN！噢  KVN！
KVN! Oh, KVN!
蓋瑞？蓋瑞？蓋瑞？
Gary? Gary? Gary?!
蓋瑞  蓋瑞  蓋瑞
Gary? Gary. Gary!
蓋瑞  睡著了嗎？
Gary, are you sleeping?
Wah-pa!
哦  好吧  我不搞了  不要打我
Oh, okay. We're good. Don't mind me.
我  我只是要往這邊飛
I'm -- I'm just floating this way.
我是要去這邊的
This is the way I'd like to go.
拜拜  我計劃是走這邊的  這是我的路線
Bye! This was my plan. That's my path.
所有的碎片都集齊了
All the pieces are in place.
我就陪你玩一玩吧
Let's play a little.